sc2ranks.com 2015-06-11

# Global Rankings - Starcraft 2 Ranks

  1. **Website Visitors**

Like most website operators, SC2Ranks collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. SC2Ranks’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how SC2Ranks’s visitors use its website. From time to time, SC2Ranks may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website. SC2Ranks also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. SC2Ranks only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below. 

  2. **Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information**

Certain visitors to SC2Ranks’s websites choose to interact with SC2Ranks in ways that require SC2Ranks to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that SC2Ranks gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask customers who create accounts for the purposes of obtaining a portfolio site to provide an email address. Those who engage in transactions with SC2Ranks – by purchasing subscriptions, for example – are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, SC2Ranks collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the customer’s interaction with SC2Ranks. SC2Ranks does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. Customers can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities. 

  3. **Aggregated Statistics**

SC2Ranks may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. For instance, SC2Ranks may monitor individual or aggregate portfolio site usage, and display that number in aggregate on the SC2Ranks website. However, SC2Ranks does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. 

  4. **Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information**

SC2Ranks discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on SC2Ranks’s behalf or to provide services available at SC2Ranks’s websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using SC2Ranks’s websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. SC2Ranks will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, SC2Ranks discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when SC2Ranks believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of SC2Ranks, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of an SC2Ranks website and have supplied your email address, SC2Ranks may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with SC2Ranks and our products. We primarily use our blog to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. SC2Ranks takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information. 

  5. **Cookies**

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. SC2Ranks uses cookies to help SC2Ranks identify and track visitors, their usage of SC2Ranks website, and their website access preferences. SC2Ranks visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using SC2Ranks’s websites, knowing that you will not be able to sign in or use certain features of SC2Ranks at all. 

  6. **Privacy Policy Changes**

SC2Ranks may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and at SC2Ranks’s sole discretion. Visitrs are encouraged frequently check this page for any changes to SC2Ranks's Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
